exitravel.com 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy

exitnow.ca uses the highest-level security features available to ensure your personal information is never revealed to unauthorized parties. When you provide us with any personal information - your name, address, e-mail and credit card number - it's handled by a server secured with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). SSL is a technology provided by VeriSign, a worldwide industry leader in advanced e-commerce security systems.

Guarantee

We are confident it's secure to book a vacation online on exitnow.ca. In fact, we're so confident that we offer the following guarantee.

Most credit card companies in North America will remove any proven unauthorized charges made on your credit card. Some of them, however, require you to pay the first $50, referred to as a deductible, of any unauthorized charge. If your credit card company holds you liable for a deductible due to a proven unauthorized charge on exitnow.ca, we guarantee that we will pay the entire deductible up to $50. We cover this liability, provided the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own and was a result of purchases made on exitnow.ca.

Terms and conditions

When buying a holiday online, it's important that you understand exactly what to expect. And that's precisely what the Terms and conditions are all about. Developed according to the best practices in the leisure travel industry, the Terms and conditions give you a detailed understanding of specific procedures when you travel with exitnow.ca. Keep in mind that using exitnow.ca automatically means that you agree with these terms and conditions.

Exitnow.ca is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information and has taken measures to ensure the privacy and confidentiality of that information. Our commitment to safeguarding your privacy is reflected in our Transat's privacy policy. We have developed this policy and related procedures to comply with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Document Act. We invite you to consult our privacy policy for more information and details. We invite you to consult our privacy policy to get more details, it is accessible below.

Exitnow.ca is responsible for personal information it holds or has under its control, including personal information it passes to others with your permission. Our privacy officer will receive and respond to your enquiries and complaints regarding the protection and privacy of your personal information, and will deal with requests for access to your information.

1\. The importance of the right to privacy.

Transat takes the privacy rights of individuals very seriously and, in this respect, takes all measures possible to ensure the protection of the personal information that we collect in providing our services. Transat may be required to exchange personal information with third parties on individuals for the purpose of administering customer accounts and files. Transat and such third parties may also exchange information on individuals that is not of a sensitive nature regarding their preferences for the purpose of offering and providing quality benefits, products, goods, and services in an efficient manner. Nevertheless, Transat will not collect, use, or disclose any personal information on an individual without his or her consent, unless compelled to do so by statute or regulation. In this regard, our primary concern is the trust that individuals place in our safeguarding the privacy of their personal information.

The purpose of this Policy is to outline our commitment regarding the protection of privacy as well as the rules we intend to follow when we collect, retain, use, or disclose personal information.

Our Policy has been formulated to satisfy and indeed, even to exceed the requirements of privacy legislation in force in Canada, specifically the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, S.C. 2000, c. 5, various provincial laws regarding privacy protection, the Principles set out in the National Standard of Canada for the Protection of Personal Information (CAN/CSA-Q830-96), as well as any applicable regulations (hereinafter the "Law"). We also undertake to constantly re-assess our rules of practice and our procedures in this area and to take into account the comments of any individuals.

In order to better understand and meet the expectations of individuals regarding the protection of personal information, Transat has designated a member of senior management to act as Director, Protection of Personal Information (hereinafter "the Director"). Any person may contact the Director in order to share comments, request access to any personal information that we may have on him or her, request that corrections be made to the information, or to file a complaint. The Director shall conduct a consistent review of Transat practices and procedures to ensure compliance with this Policy and to meet customer expectations in this respect.

2\. Transat's undertakings

      a.     We shall collect only such personal information as is required to offer services, benefits, goods, and products to individuals;  
      b.     We shall not disclose any personal information to a third party without the prior express or tacit consent, as applicable, of the individual, or unless bound by law to do so;  
      c.     We shall not collect, use, or disclose any personal information on any individual without having obtained his or her prior express or tacit consent, as applicable, or unless bound by any statute or regulation to do so;  
      d.     We may on occasion release personal information to our external agencies or mandataries for processing, to identify customers likely to be interested in benefits, products, goods, or services offered by Transat. Through contractual agreements or other comparable means, we shall ensure that your personal information is protected when processed by our mandataries and external agencies;  
      e.     In order to increase the opportunities of Transat customers to obtain special benefits, we may occasionally exchange personal information with a third party, in the form of a list of those customers who meet certain general criteria. The lists may not contain any information of a sensitive nature, and the use of such information by the third party for any purpose other than as set forth in this Policy is strictly prohibited. Under no circumstances may personal information be disclosed without the express or tacit consent, as applicable of the individual concerned.  
      f.     We will provide individuals with explanations on how to delete their names from any lists we exchange with third parties. Individuals may contact us at any time to have their names removed from these lists;  
      g.     We guarantee the security and confidentiality of the information that individuals provide us with. Compliance with these standards is subject to audit and these standards may be revised where a situation warrants it;  
      h.     If requested to reveal personal information to a third party, we shall assume responsibility for the disclosures and shall take the necessary measures to ensure that the undertakings and rules referred to in this Policy are observed by this third party;  
      i.     We require that all organizations that provide us with administrative support services or that process information at our request comply with the undertakings and rules contained in this Policy; and  
      j.     Any individual is entitled to take cognizance of the information we hold on him or her, subject to restrictions in the Law, and that person may require that inaccurate or incomplete information be corrected. Where applicable, we shall transmit this information to the person concerned and shall make the necessary corrections without delay.

3\. Transat's Rules regarding the Protection of Personal Information.

      A.     Personal information  
      The following is regarded as personal information: any information that is directly connected to an identifiable person including, but not limited to, his or her name, residential address, social insurance number, as well as any information relating to his or her medical condition or financial situation.  
      B.     Responsibilities  
      Transat is responsible for the personal information in its possession or under its control, in particular, personal information that it entrusts to its mandataries, agents or representatives. Transat shall adopt and apply specific rules of conduct and procedures that ensure compliance with the undertakings and rules referred to in this Policy, which, inter alia, are as follows:  
      i.     The Director shall take all measures necessary to ensure that the undertakings regarding privacy rights and the protection of personal information, as well as the rules contained in this Policy, are complied with by Transat employees and its agents, mandataries or representatives;  
      ii.     Transat shall require that all agents, mandataries, representatives and other external organizations required to provide it with administrative support services, agree, either by contract or through a certificate of compliance, to comply with the undertakings and rules referred to in this Policy. They are prohibited from using the personal information held by Transat for purposes other than those for which the information was provided to them. The aforementioned phrase "agents, mandataries, representatives, and other organizations" includes, in particular, Transat suppliers of hotel and airport services, data processing and storage companies, as well as suppliers of administrative support services;  
      iii.     Transat shall implement security measures to ensure the confidentiality of personal information;  
      iv.     Transat shall issue employee directives to remind all staff of their obligation to comply with this Policy. In addition, Transat shall provide employee training to ensure that all staff understand the importance of privacy and how to ensure its protection;  
      v.     Transat shall periodically remind third parties with whom it does business that they, their agents, mandataries or representatives must comply with the undertakings and rules referred to in this Policy; and  
      vi.     Transat has adopted procedures in order to receive and investigate complaints, and must report back to complainants as soon as possible.  
      C.     Identification of uses for which personal information is collected  
      Transat may collect personal information on individuals but solely for the purposes identified in advance.  
      i.     Transat may collect personal information for the following purposes:

          (a) to check the identity of individuals, to contact them, and to communicate with them;

          (b) to better understand the preferences, needs, and interests of individuals.

          (c) to enable Transat to offer individuals services, benefits, products, and goods within the framework of this Policy;

          (d) to comply with the statutes and regulations in force, including the information requirements of customs and immigration control, and to ensure the security and the processing of information; and

          (e) to allow Transat to effectively manage its human resources.  
      D.     Restrictions relating to the collection of personal information  
      Transat may collect only such personal information as is necessary for the purposes identified in this Policy. Furthermore, Transat may only collect personal information by employing legal and legitimate means.  
      i.     Transat may collect personal information from the following sources:

          (a) customers;

          (b) agents, mandataries or representatives;

          (c) employees; and

          (d) suppliers.  
      ii.     In responding to offers made by third parties with whom Transat may do business (whether sent to customers by these parties or by Transat), individuals may be asked to provide personal. The transmission of information by individuals to, and the collection thereof by the third parties does not constitute collection of personal information by Transat and is therefore exclusively under the control of the individuals and the third parties in question.  
      E.     Identification of uses and disclosure of personal information  
      Transat may use or disclose personal information solely for the purposes identified in advance and by employing the means also thus identified. Transat may not collect, use, or disclose any personal information concerning an individual without his or her express or tacit consent, as applicable, unless required to do so by statute or regulation.  
      Transat shall not use or disclose any personal information except for the following purposes, and in the manner indicated:  
      i.     Personal information, that is not sensitive in nature (N.B. information will be deemed as being sensitive of the purpose of applying the present Policy where such information refers to the health or physical, mental or medical condition of an individual), regarding customers' preferences, needs, and interests, may be used to identify those customers who are most likely to be interested in products or services offered by Transat and its agents, mandataries or representatives. Such information shall be used exclusively to enable Transat and its agents, mandataries or agents to propose services, premiums, benefits, and products that are likely to interest customers as part of a Transat promotional offer. Transat may not provide individualized customer profiles to third parties.  
      ii.     When a third party wishes to submit an offer to customers, generally the offer shall be sent to customers by Transat rather than by the party in question.  
      iii.     However, for follow-up purposes, Transat may on occasion provide a third party with a list of customers to whom an offer was transmitted. Occasionally, Transat may also provide such a party with a list of customers who meet certain general criteria involving non-sensitive information, while ensuring through contractual or other means that the third party is strictly prohibited from using the list for any purpose other than to offer customers a benefit or a privilege available exclusively to Transat customers.

          The use of a customer list by a third party for any other purpose is forbidden. Information of a sensitive nature may not be disclosed under any circumstances without the express consent of the individual.  
      iv.     Personal information may be disclosed to agents, mandataries, representatives, or to other organizations whose services are retained by Transat. The agents, mandataries, representatives, and other organizations must sign a confidentiality agreement. They may not use the information transmitted to them except for the purposes referred to in the agreement. These parties are formally prohibited from disclosing the information in question to other third parties without the prior consent of Transat.  
      v.     Personal information may be disclosed when required by statute or regulation.  
      F.     Restrictions concerning the use, disclosure, and the retention of personal information  
      Transat may not use or disclose personal information for any purpose other than that for which it was collected, unless the express or tacit consent, as applicable, of the individual concerned has been obtained or unless the Law requires the use of disclosure of such information. Furthermore, Transat may not retain personal information except as required to achieve the purposes identified.  
      G.     Consent  
      Transat shall take all measures necessary to ensure that individuals know and understand the purposes for which it collects, uses, or discloses personal information. Transat shall obtain the consent of every individual in respect of whom it collects, uses, or discloses personal information. Indeed, depending on the circumstances and the nature of the information, such consent may be express or tacit. In certain circumstances, express consent is necessary. In other cases, consent is reasonably presumed, but is revocable on demand.  
      i.     Transat may not collect, use, or disclose any sensitive personal information of an individual without the express consent of the person concerned, unless required to do so by statute or regulation;  
      ii.     Transat shall periodically inform individuals by correspondence, through its Web site or interactive voice response system of any change to this Policy on the protection of personal information and the right to privacy, as well as any further collection, use, or disclosure of personal information in order to obtain the appropriate consent. Transat shall use a combination of the aforementioned methods to ensure that all necessary measures are taken to contact the individuals concerned;  
      iii.     When customers fill out a survey from Transat, its agents, mandataries or representatives, concerning their preferences, needs, or interests, they will be advised of the specific reasons for which the personal information was collected, used, or disclosed. The survey shall contain a statement reminding the customer that in completing and returning the survey, he or she is consenting to the collection, use, and disclosure of information provided through the survey for the purposes identified therein.  
      H.     Accuracy of personal information  
      Transat veillera à prendre les mesures nécessaires pour s'assurer que les renseignements personnels qu'elle détient au sujet des individus sont à jour et en fonction de l'usage auquel ils sont destinés.  
      i.     Transat shall ensure that the necessary measures are taken to ensure that the personal information it has on individuals is up to date and accurately reflects its intended use.  
      ii.     Transat may not systematically update personal information unless it is necessary for achieving the purpose for which the information was collected. These updates shall be carried out in compliance with Section D above; and  
      iii.     Since it is quicker and more efficient for individuals to inform Transat of any changes to their personal information, such as their names or addresses, Transat shall ask the individuals concerned to ensure that the information they provide is up to date and accurate, and wherever possible, that they inform Transat of any changes.  
      I.     Measures for ensuring the security of personal information  
      Transat ensures the protection of personal information by relying on physical, technological, and administrative security measures.  
      i.     The security measures put in place by Transat are intended to protect personal information against loss or theft, and safeguard it from unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or modification;  
      ii.     To ensure the confidentiality of personal information, Transat shall employ a) physical measures such as locked filing cabinets and restricting access to its offices; b) administrative measures such as security clearances and limiting access on a "need to know" basis for individuals, agents, mandataries, and representatives; and c) technical and technological measures. When it uses information technologies such as the Internet, Transat shall remind individuals, agents, mandataries or representatives of the importance of protecting the confidentiality of personal information; and  
      iii.     Transat shall put in place all measures necessary to ensure the destruction and safe disposal of personal information.  
      J.     Transparency  
      Transat shall ensure that this Policy and the undertakings and rules of practice and procedure concerning the management of personal information set forth herein are readily accessible to anyone, especially its customers. Copies of this Policy may be obtained from the Director at any time on request. This Policy is also available on the Internet.  
      K.     Access to personal information  
      Any individual making a request in writing is entitled to be informed of the existence of personal information held by Transat on him or her, of the use made of such information and of the fact that this information was provided to third parties. The individual concerned is also entitled to access such information, subject to legislative and regulatory exceptions. The individual may also contest the accuracy or completeness of information and request that corrections be made. To exercise their right of access or of correction, the individuals concerned should contact Mr. George Petsikas, Director, Protection of Personal Information, Transat at the following address: 5959, boulevard de la Côte-Vertu, Montréal, Québec H4S 2E6.  
      i.     The applicant must identify himself or herself, provide his or her employee number (where applicable) and sign the request in order to prevent fraud or the unjustified transmission of personal information to a third party. The individual concerned shall provide sufficient information to enable Transat to confirm the existence of such personal information, to inform the applicant of the use thereof and to provide access thereto;  
      ii.     Transat shall process the request for access to or correction of personal information within thirty (30) days of receiving the request. This time limit may be extended by an additional period of thirty (30) days if processing the request would unreasonably interfere with Transat activities or if circumstances or the scope of the request make it impossible to meet this deadline;  
      iii.     Generally, Transat shall grant the applicant access to the personal information on him or her, or correct the information at no charge. It may, however, be necessary to charge a reasonable fee to recover any administrative costs or when the request for access to information or correction of information is complex.  
      iv.     With regard to the correction of personal information, Transat shall do so where the applicant can establish the incomplete nature or the inaccuracy of the information. As required, correction may involve a correction, withdrawal, or the addition of information; and  
      v.     Should the applicant be dissatisfied with the answer to a request for access to or correction of information, he or she may file a complaint with the Director.  
      L.     Complaints concerning non-compliance with the Policy  
      Should an individual feel that this Policy is not being complied with or should he or she be concerned by Transat practices, the individual concerned may submit a complaint to Transat by sending it to Mr. George Petsikas, Director, Protection of Personal Information, Transat.  
      i.     A complaint or request for an inquiry must be addressed in writing to the Director at the following address: 5959, boulevard de la Côte-Vertu, Montréal, Québec H4S 2E6; and  
      ii.     Any complaint or request for investigation shall be the subject of an inquiry or a reply within sixty (60) working days. If the complaint is justified, Transat will take the appropriate follow-up measures including providing access to the personal information requested, the correction of the information, or, where applicable, by modifying this Policy.

This website (the "Site") provides information with respect to Exitnow.ca. Please read the following terms and conditions of the use of this Site closely. Your use of this Site is subject to all terms and conditions therein set forth as well as other terms and conditions set out elsewhere on this Site, as the same may be modified from time to time at Exitnow.ca' sole discretion without notice. Your use of this Site constitutes your acceptance of all such terms and conditions and your agreement to be bound thereby. You may terminate your agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions hereof by ceasing to use this Site and by destroying all information obtained from this Site together with any copies thereof and related documentation. Exitnow.ca may terminate the agreement constituted by your use of this Site at any time without notice if you breach any terms or conditions of the use of this Site. Such termination is without prejudice to all other rights and remedies which Exitnow.ca may have at law as a result of your violation of the terms and conditions of the use of this Site.

Jurisdiction  
This Site is operated and controlled in Canada. This agreement shall be governed by and is construed in accordance with the laws of the Province of Quebec without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of law. If any provision of this agreement be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this agreement and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions.

Use of Information  
If you respond to this Site with questions, comments, suggestions or feedback with respect to the content of this Site, all such questions, comments, suggestions or feedback ("Information") shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Exitnow.ca shall have no obligations whatsoever with respect to such Information and shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose or distribute the Information without limitation and without your consent or approval. In addition, Exitnow.ca shall be entitled, but not obligated, to use, without compensation paid, any ideas, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in such Information for any purpose whatsoever including, but not limited to, developing and marketing services, incorporating such Information.

Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability  
Exitnow.ca uses all commercially reasonable efforts to provide accurate information, but does not guarantee it and makes no representation regarding its accuracy, reliability or any other matter. Unless otherwise specified, the materials on this Site is presented solely for the purpose of promoting Exitnow.ca' products. Exitnow.ca makes no representation that materials and products are available in all locations and on the dates indicated. Flight schedules and destinations may also be subject to change. It is your sole responsibility to confirm the accuracy and currency of the information relating to scheduling and destination before relying on it. Exitnow.ca does not guarantee that this Site or every feature of this Site will remain available to you. Neither Exitnow.ca nor anyone who helped develop, create, produce or deliver the material or information on this Site or the functionality of this Site warrants that the functions contained in this Site will be uninterrupted or error free, that defects will be corrected, that this Site or any server that makes it available is free from viruses or other harmful components or that successful results or outcomes will result from your use of information of this Site. Without limiting the foregoing, all information on this Site is provided on an "as is" basis without warrant of any kind, either expressed or implied, including but not limited to any implied warranties as to accuracy, timeliness, completeness, merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. Exitnow.ca is not responsible for any material posted on this Site by any user or for any information whatsoever contained in any linked Site. Exitnow.ca is not responsible or liable for any defamatory, offensive or illegal conduct of any other visitor to this Site or any third party. IN NO EVENT, WILL EXITNOW.CA BE LIABLE TO USERS AND/OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RELATED TO OR ARISING FROM THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THIS SITE OR ANY INFORMATION OR MATERIAL ON THIS SITE. WITHOUT LIMITING THE GENERALITY OF THE FOREGOING, EXITNOW.CA SHALL NOT UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES BE LIABLE TO USERS AND/OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY LOSS OF PROFITS OR LOSS OF OPPORTUNITIES, INDIRECT, DIRECT, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, EVEN IF EXITNOW.CA HAS BEEN ADVISED OR WAS OR SHOULD HAVE BEEN AWARE OF THE POSSIBLITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. The use of this website and/or the information contained on this website is entirely and completely at the customer's own risk. If the customer accesses the Site through a link to a non-Exitnow.ca' website, and such site is for the booking of different products, Exitnow.ca invites the customer to read carefully the terms and conditions specifically specified in such linked website.

Copyright and Trademarks  
All information and artwork on this Site are protected by copyright. All pictures on this Site are either owned by Exitnow.ca or used with permission. Exitnow.ca retains full and complete title to all downloadable software and all images incorporated or generated by the software. You may make a hard copy or download the material for personal use only. You may not reproduce, transmit, distribute, display, download, copy, reproduce or use on your website or in any other public or commercial manner any information, images, sequences contained herein, graphics or functionality from this website including, without limitation, for purposes of producing a television report, producing a website or publishing a poster, advertisement or brochure, without the prior express written consent of Exitnow.ca. You may not reverse-engineer, disassemble or otherwise convert any component of this website to another form. Unless otherwise specified, all trademarks used on this Site are the property of Exitnow.ca or another party and in the latter case are licensed to Exitnow.ca for use in association with its operations. This website is a production and the sole and exclusive property of Exitnow.ca.

exitnow.ca Terms and Conditions

1\. exitnow.ca's responsibility

Once you have booked your vacation, exitnow.ca will send your confirmation instantly by e-mail and we will send your travel documents as soon as we receive them from your designated airline or tour operator. (See "Document delivery" for more details)  
exitnow.ca takes the utmost care to ensure that the information on its site is accurate.

exitnow.ca is provided solely to assist customers in determining the availability of travel-related goods and services and to make legitimate reservations and purchases.

Once you have booked your vacation, exitnow.ca will send you an invoice and will provide you with your ticket and other travel documents in accordance with the provisions of section 5 of the terms and conditions of exitnow.ca.

2\. User's responsibility

You, the user, warrant that you are at least 18 years of age and possess the legal authority to enter into this agreement and to use this Web site in accordance with all terms and conditions herein.

You agree to be financially responsible for all of your use of the exitnow.ca site, as well as for use of your account by others, including without limitation minors living with you. You agree to supervise all usage by minors of this Web site under your name or account.

You also warrant that all information supplied by you or members of your household in using this Web site is true and accurate.

Travel documents

All trips outside Canada require a valid Canadian passport and travel to certain countries may require you to hold a passport that is valid for six months beyond the date of the expected return to Canada. Canadian citizens born in certain countries may require a visa in addition to a valid passport. A permanent resident card will be required for permanent residents /landed immigrants who are not Canadian citizens. Certain countries may restrict the entry of unaccompanied minors by one guardian only. One (1) parent travelling with a child under the age of 18 may have to obtain a notarized letter of consent signed by the parent not travelling. More information on required travel documents is available at www.voyage.gc.ca. It is your responsibility to ensure that you have the appropriate travel documentation, and then make certain that you have those necessary documents in hand prior to departure. If you are unsure about the information provided regarding the documentation required, you should contact exitnow.ca. Failure to have the required travel documents may cause you to be denied boarding privileges by the carrier or relevant authorities, without further recourse or the possibility of a refund. Entry to another country may also be refused even if the required information and travel documents are complete.

Travelling to the United States

In addition to the Advance Passenger Information System (APIS) requirement noted above, until January 22, 2007 Canadian citizens will require a valid passport or proof of Canadian citizenship with official photo ID As of January 23, 2007, the United States will require all travellers to present a passport or other appropriate secure document (see link for list) when entering or re-entering the United States by air or sea. For more information, consult http://www.cbsa-asfc.gc.ca/agency/whti-ivho/what-quoi-e.html.

A Visa Waiver Program exists for certain countries. However, travellers from certain countries require additional visas to enter the U.S. For more information visit http://ottawa.usembassy.gov/content/content.asp?section=travel&document=landed_newrequirements_021803

Visa Waiver Program (VWP)

The Visa Waiver Program (VWP) enables nationals of certain countries to travel to the United States for tourism or business for stays of 90 days or less without obtaining a visa. All VWP travelers, regardless of age or type of passport used, must present machine-readable passports. For more information, consult http://www.travel.state.gov/visa/temp/without/without_1990.html  
All passengers, regardless of nationality, must verify their individual requirements with their travel agent and the U.S. Consulate prior to departure.

Personal and non-commercial use limitation

The exitnow.ca site is for your personal use only, and not for any commercial purposes. You may not modify, copy, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, create derivative works from, transfer, or sell any information, software, products, or services obtained from the exitnow.ca site.

You may only use this site to look for information on available travel-related goods and services, make legitimate reservations or purchases and shall not use this site to make any speculative, false or fraudulent reservation or any reservation in anticipation of demand.

violation of rules and regulations

exitnow.ca expects from you that you will not use this Web site for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these terms, conditions and notices. You understand that abuse of the travel services reservation facilities of the Web site may result in you being denied access to such facilities.

3\. Privacy and confidentiality

Respecting the privacy of our customers is one of exitnow.ca greatest concerns. We do not sell individual customer names or other private profile information to third parties and have no intention to do so in the future. In fact, all direct communication with exitnow.ca (be it via e-mail, fax phone or mail) is kept confidential. We respect and will continue to respect your privacy. To book your vacation, however, we do need a minimal amount of personal information to process your transactions.

When you reserve or purchase travel services through exitnow.ca we are required to provide basic information (such as name and address) about you and your purchase to the designated tour operator, airline, or any other travel service provider. This ensures the successful fulfillment of your travel arrangements. Again, at exitnow.ca, everything is done to respect your privacy. You understand that in order to verify your personal information, exitnow.ca may disclose it to third parties and that such third parties may provide verification of such personal information to exitnow.ca from information they have previously collected about you.

exitnow.ca will not send you any unsolicited information. Should you become a member of one of our various programs, you will receive information from us only as we originally indicated to you.

4\. Payment

Residents of Canada and of the United States can pay online, or by phone using Visa, American Express or MasterCard.  
When you reserve, full payment is required and will be debited from your credit card account. You will be notified with the invoice that will be transmitted upon reservation.

The purchase is 100 percent non-refundable, non-transferable and no changes are permitted by the purchaser or passengers.

The booking of travel services constitutes a contract between the customer and exitnow.ca, operating under Transat Distribution Canada inc. Unless the customer has paid in full, all prices may be increased at any time and for any reason. Where there is an increase in the total price of travel services after a deposit has been paid and the cumulative increase, except any increase resulting from an increase in retail sales tax or federal goods and services tax, is more than seven per cent (7%), the customer has the right to cancel the contract and obtain a full refund.

If you are a Quebec resident, an amount of 3.50$ per 1000$ of travel services purchased is added to your invoice for your contribution to the Indemnity Fund.

The administration and invoicing for your booking is done by exitnow.ca in collaboration with Transat Distribution Canada.

5\. Document delivery

After you have completed your booking, exitnow.ca will send you an invoice confirming your itinerary and details of your booking. It is then your last chance to verify that the information written on your travel documents is accurate.

If you purchased an insurance policy, you will receive your documents through regular mail. A complete booklet and personalized card will be sent to you. You should keep this card on you during your entire trip.

For delivery of your documents, three options are offered to you:

   1\. messenger delivery ($20.00);  
   2\. pick-up at one of our offices (Montreal or Toronto) at no charge;  
   3\. pick-up at the airport at no charge.

Please note that options (1) and (2) above can only be retained if the reservation is made more than fourteen (14) days prior to departure. Your documents will be transmitted to you within two (2) weeks of your departure, as the case may be. If your reservation is made fourteen (14) days or less prior to departure, the only possible travel document delivery mode is option (3).

7\. Insurance

For each transaction made by customers residing in Canada, exitnow.ca offers travel insurance coverage, including trip cancellation insurance and out-of-province health insurance. You acknowledge that exitnow.ca made this offer in good faith and that you are fully responsible for your decisions in regard to insurance (i.e. either not buying any insurance whatsoever or buying the full insurance package).

Once you have booked a reservation, you can buy travel insurance or increase the coverage of the insurance package you already bought within 48 hours. If you decide to cancel the insurance package you bought through exitnow.ca, you have to advise us within a period of 10 days.

In any and all situations, which warrant filing an insurance claim, the user is instructed to contact exitnow.ca as soon as possible.

For each transaction made by customers living in the United States, you must contact a local company to buy insurance packages.

7\. Prohibited airline carriers

In accordance with the article 9.3 of the European regulations, please find hereafter the list of airline companies banned within the European territory.  
http://ec.europa.eu/transport/air/safety/doc/flywell/2006_06_20_flywell_list_en.pdf

8\. Customer advisory

Living standards and practices at the destination and the standards and conditions there with respect to the provision of utilities, services and accommodation may differ from those found in Canada.

For any question relating to your online booking, please contact exitnow.ca at 1 866 561-3948.

exitnow.ca is a division of Transat Distribution Canada Inc.  
Transat Distribution Canada Inc. is registered as a retail travel agent in Québec (753141) and Ontario (50015084) with offices located in Montréal : Place du Parc, 300, rue Léo-Pariseau, bureau 1601, Montréal (Québec) H2X 4B3 ; in Toronto au 5090 Explorer Drive, Suite 800, Mississauga, Ontario L4W 4T9.

January, 2007
